anticoagulationuk.org 2018-09-29

# Anticoagulation UK

We are required to inform all contacts about the practices that will govern the processing of personal data.

**Information collection and use**  

Anticoagulation UK may collect personal information from you when you enquire about our activities, register with us, make a donation or otherwise provide us with personal data. Anticoagulation UK may use this information to provide you with the information, services or products that you have requested, for administration purposes and to contact you.

Anticoagulation UK take appropriate measures to ensure that the information disclosed to us is kept secure, accurate and up to date and that it is kept only for so long as is necessary for the purposes for which it is used.

**Information sharing and disclosure**

Anticoagulation UK will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone. Anticoagulation UK may send personal information to other agencies or organisations if we obtain your consent.

Anticoagulation UK may also disclose your personal information if your actions violate the terms of use of this website, or if required to do so by law.  Anticoagulation UK does not operate direct marketing activities. All information you receive will be at your personal request.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of information sent by an organisation's website to your computer and stored on your hard drive. They are used to track repeat visits and other data. To find out more, please read our cookie policy.

**Your consent**

By providing us with your personal data, including sensitive personal data such as health information, you consent to the collection and use of any information you provide in accordance with this privacy statement.  No personal information will be shared outside of ACUK without your explicit consent.

**Right of access**

You have the right to ask for a copy of the information we hold about you and to have any inaccuracies corrected. Anticoagulation UK may charge a small fee for this.

**Changes**

Please help Anticoagulation UK keep your information up to date by notifying any changes to: 

By post to: Anticoagulation UK, ACE House, 2 Appledore Close, Bromley, Kent BR2 9WBZ 

By email to:  [contact@anticoagulationuk.org](mailto:contact@anticoagulationuk.org)

If you are a registered member of AntiCoagulation UK, you can edit your online profile by logging into the site. 

Anticoagulation UK reserve the right to amend this privacy statement at any time by updating the text on this website and you will be deemed to have accepted such changes. 

**Anticoagulation UK**

**Privacy statement revised on the 16 th May 2018**
